<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Belajar Blog on Saeful Rahman</title>
    <link>https://saefulrahman.my.id/blog/category/belajar-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Belajar Blog on Saeful Rahman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 16:40:27 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://saefulrahman.my.id/blog/category/belajar-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Web Development Frameworks</title>
      <link>https://saefulrahman.my.id/blog/10-best-web-development-frameworks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 16:40:27 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saefulrahman.my.id/blog/10-best-web-development-frameworks/</guid>
      <description>Daftar Isi     Heading 1 Multiple frameworks have been invented Pull Quote tag to simplify the web development process, increase flexibility and reduce time to market. Without the use of frameworks, modern web development would be a nightmare for software engineers because they would have to create databases, business logic, security options, and many other things from scratch.
This article talks about the essence of web development frameworks and provides a list of the most popular web frameworks for 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 27 Best Websites for Wasting Time on the Internet in 2021</title>
      <link>https://saefulrahman.my.id/blog/recommended-website-for-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 11:49:27 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saefulrahman.my.id/blog/recommended-website-for-developer/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of content out there about productivity &amp;ndash; everything from hacks to shortcuts to tips and tricks for how to get more done in less time.
It&amp;rsquo;s all about the sprint, the checking things off the list, and the downloading of software that&amp;rsquo;ll block out any and all distractions.
But what about those times when you just want to surf the internet aimlessly? No one can be hyper-productive all the time, and studies have shown that taking deliberate breaks after periods of work is actually better for your productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
